DHWANI NAIK

9717688806 | dhwaninaik99@icloud.com | Vadodara, Gujarat 390008

SUMMARY

Astute and meticulously creative personnel with majors in Economics and Business, along with a demonstrated history of diversified work experience in the areas of Market Analysis, Sales and Public Relations. Strategic thinker, adept at creative problem solving and deriving customer focused solutions.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer Service & PR Executive , Writer's Pocket , September 2022-December 2022

Vadodara, India

- Engaged as the Single Point of Contact as the Sales Head, while elevating brand perception by catering to all clients and prospective leads.
- Generated sales upwards of Rs. 80,000 in 3 months time by converting cold leads into closed book deals, worth an average of 30 authors per month.
- Responsible for fielding 80+ cold calls a week along with addressing client redressal enquires.
- Crafted Customized packages by analyzing consumer insights (both primary and secondary).

Board Member, Sustainaibility Concordia, September 2021-July 2022

Montreal

- Engaged as an elected Board Member, at an independent organization working on Sustainability, Environmental awareness and protecting the rights of Indigenous People.
- Established excellent relationships with city residents and students at the Concordia university campus.
- Worked as part of the public outreach committee, and worked to organize campaigns, design promotional materials and allocate budgets to events spread across the year.

Board Member, QPIRG Concordia, October 2021-June 2022

Montreal

- Elected as a Board member for the Quebec Public Interest Research Group (QPIRG), at Concordia.
- Raised awareness and supported grassroots level activism around diverse social and environmental issues.
- Collected funds for organization through community outreach initiatives, planned events and allocated funds to other NGOs across Ouebec.

Call Centre Agent, Tele Sondage Plus, October 2021-February 2022

Montreal

- Assisted 3 third party companies on a monthly basis, (project based) by reporting customer satisfaction data & relaying relevant data driven remarks.
- Reported insights by interpreting surveys for a market research company, across North America.
- Answered, screened and processed 100-200 calls a week to conduct surveys, address customer needs and conduct relevant data entries.

• Resolved customer inquiries to consistently offer quality service and meet performance benchmarks.

Finance and Strategy Intern, ND International, August 2020-July 2021

Vadodara, Gujarat

- Tasked with aiding the finance department to maintain 50 client account reports, preparing monthly reconciliation statements and studying the export import market in depth; in order to identify variables and supplement the policy decisions of, purchase and supply.
- Was part of a core team, to identify key business drivers by scrutinizing the chemical trading industry, with a focus on trade with Middle Eastern and Asian countries in particular.
- Provided clerical support by handling a range of functions such as market research, customer demand appreciation and other routine administrative tasks.
- Sorted and organized files, spreadsheets and reports.

Marketing Intern, Future Link Consultants, July 2020-August 2020

Toronto And Vadodara

- Part of the Online Sales Department, and also tasked as a Counselor for students aiming to pursue higher education.
- Conducted cold calling on a daily basis, (an average of 70-100) to expand the client database and conducted online and in person counseling.
- Responsible for strategizing and executing promotion strategies for online marketing of the company (through Instagram).
- Aided in designing specific marketing materials for social media marketing in general as well, through Google AdWords and SEO.

EDUCATION

CFA level 1, 2023 onwards

Graduate Diploma

Economics, Concordia University, Montreal QC December 2022

- Dropped out, before the final semester due to a personal medical issue. Finished two semesters however.
- Program GPA: 3.17/4.00
- Relevant coursework Completed: Urban Economics, Advanced Macroeconomic Theory, Advanced Microeconomic Theory, Advanced Environmental Economics, Economic Development and Transportation Economics.
- Elected as Board member of QPIRG at Concordia and Sustainability at Concordia.

B.B.A. (Bachelor of Business Administration)

Business Administration, Navarachana University, Vadodara, Gujarat June 2020

- Awarded the certification for receiving the second highest CGPA in the batch- 8.62/10.
- Head of the Public Relations Committee for the years 2017-2021, at Business at NUV, a business school student committee.
- Assistant Content Initiator for the Annual Magazine.

Senior School Certificate

Navarachana Higher Secondary School, Vadodara, Gujarat, India. June 2017

GPA: 77.8%,

Relevvant coursework completed in Math, Economics, Business Studies, English and Accountancy.

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Highest CGPA: Navrachana University. (BBA program).
- 3rd position: Nationals, TIE Global
 Secured the 3rd position in a global entrepreneurship competition, held at IIM Ahemdabad; as part of a team, organized by Times Indus Entrepreneurs, a global organization; headquartered in the Silicon Valley.
- Participated in a 6 month Entrepreneurship workshop: Organized by a Silicon valley Incubator: TIE, at Ahemdabad.
- Participated in Model United Nations Conferences: IIMUN, IYMUN and NAVMUN.

SKILLS

- Communications Strategies
- Critical Thinking
- Business Development
- Quantitative Analysis

- Social Media Marketing
- Salesforce CRM Software
- Brand creation and narrative setting
- Content Management Expertise

LANGUAGES

English, Hindi, Gujarati: First Language

French: A2

Elementary

LINKEDIN

• https://www.linkedin.com/in/dhwani-n-02959921